A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller, Vice Presidential records, National Commission on Water Quality, Series 9 FA379
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Economic Impact of the Federal Water Pollution Control Act Amendments of 1972 on the Nonferrous Metals Industry (Draft), by the National Bureau of Economic Research, June 1975 (Box 37, Folder 1163)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Economic Impact of the Federal Water Pollution Control Act Amendments of 1972 on the Nonferrous Metals Industry, by the National Bureau of Economic Research, June 1975 (Box 37, Folder 1164)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Economic Impact of the Federal Water Pollution Control Act Amendments of 1972 on the Pulp and Paper Industry, by the National Bureau of Economic Research, June 1975 (Box 37, Folder 1165)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Economic Analysis of the Impact of the 1972 Federal Water Pollution Control Act Amendments on the U.S. Iron and Steel Industry, by the National Bureau of Economic Research, August 1975; 2 copies (Box 37, Folder 1166)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Petroleum Refining: Characteristics of the Industry's Economic Environment, by the National Bureau of Economic Research, January 1975 (Box 37, Folder 1167)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Pulp and Paper: Characteristics of the Industry's Economic Environment, by the National Bureau of Economic Research, February 1975 (Box 37, Folder 1168)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - The Textile Industry: Characteristics of the Economic and Technological Environment, by the National Bureau of Economic Research, January 1975 (Box 37, Folder 1169)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Non-Ferrous Metals: Characteristics of Their Industrial Environments, by the National Bureau of Economic Research, January 1975 (Box 37, Folder 1170)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Characteristics of the Steel Industry - Baseline Projection, by the National Bureau of Economic Research, January 1975 (Box 37, Folder 1171)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - State Tax Incentives and the Annualized Cost of Pollution Control (Draft), by the National Bureau of Economic Research, January 1975 (Box 37, Folder 1172)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - State Tax Incentives: Annualized Cost of Pollution Control, by the National Bureau of Economic Research, January 1975 (Box 37, Folder 1173)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Plant Closures and the Regional Consequences of Water Pollution Control, by the National Bureau of Economic Research, June 1975 (Box 37, Folder 1174)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - The Regional Ramifications of Effluent Abatement for Selected Water-Using Industries, by the National Bureau of Economic Research, January 1975 (Box 37, Folder 1175)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Changing Water Use in Selected Manufacturing Industries (Study Done for the Institute for Water Resources, Corps of Engineers), by the National Bureau of Economic Research, December 1973 (Box 37, Folder 1176)
- Economic Impact of Water Pollution Controls on Selected Food Industries - Vol. I: Direct and Cumulative Industry Impacts (Draft), by Development Planning and Research Associates, June 1975 (Box 38, Folder 1177)
- Economic Impact of Water Pollution Controls on Selected Food Industries - Vol. I: Final Version, November 1975 (Box 38, Folder 1178)
- Economic Impact of Water Pollution Controls on Selected Food Industries - Vol. II: General Methodology (Draft), by Development Planning and Research Associates, June 1975 (Box 38, Folder 1179)
- Economic Impact of Water Pollution Controls on Selected Food Industries - Vol. II: Final Version, November 1975 (Box 38, Folder 1180)
- Economic Impact of Water Pollution Controls on Selected Food Industries - Vol. III: The Feedlot Industry (Draft), by Development Planning and Research Associates, June 1975 (Box 38, Folder 1181)
- Economic Impact of Water Pollution Controls on Selected Food Industries - Vol. III: Final Version, November 1975 (Box 38, Folder 1182)
- Economic Impact of Water Pollution Controls on Selected Food Industries - Vol. IV: The Fruit and Vegetable Processing Industry (Draft), by Development Planning and Research Associates, June 1975 (Box 38, Folder 1183)
- Economic Impact of Water Pollution Controls on Selected Food Industries - Vol. IV: Final Version, November 1975 (Box 38, Folder 1184)
- Economic Impact of Water Pollution Controls on Selected Food Industries - Vol. IV: Appendix, November 1975 (Box 38, Folder 1185)
- Economic Impact of Water Pollution Controls on Selected Food Industries - Vol. V: Meat Products - Part 1 - The Meat Packing Industry (Draft), by Development Planning and Research Associates, June 1975 (Box 38, Folder 1186)
- Economic Impact of Water Pollution Controls on Selected Food Industries - Vol. V: Part 1 - Final Version, November 1975 (Box 38, Folder 1187)
- Economic Impact of Water Pollution Controls on Selected Food Industries - Vol. V: Meat Products - Part 2 - The Meat Processing Industry (Draft), by Development Planning and Research Associates, June 1975 (Box 38, Folder 1188)
- Economic Impact of Water Pollution Controls on Selected Food Industries - Vol. V: Part 2 - Final Version, November 1975 (Box 38, Folder 1189)
- Economic Impact of Water Pollution Controls on Selected Food Industries - Vol. V: Meat Products - Part 3 - The Poultry Processing Industry (Draft), by Development Planning and Research Associates, June 1975 (Box 38, Folder 1190)
- Economic Impact of Water Pollution Controls on Selected Food Industries - Vol. V: Part 3 - Final Version, November 1975 (Box 38, Folder 1191)
- Economic Impact of Water Pollution Controls on Selected Food Industries - Vol. V: Meat Products - Part 4 - The Independent Rendering Industry (Draft), by Development Planning and Research Associates, June 1975 (Box 38, Folder 1192)
- Economic Impact of Water Pollution Controls on Selected Food Industries - Vol. V: Part 4 - Final Version, November 1975 (Box 38, Folder 1193)
- Economic Impact of Water Pollution Controls on Selected Food Industries - Vol. VI: The Dairy Processing Industry (Draft), by Development Planning and Research Associates, June 1975 (Box 38, Folder 1194)
- Economic Impact of Water Pollution Controls on Selected Food Industries - Vol. VI: Final Version, November 1975 (Box 38, Folder 1195)
- Economic Impact of Water Pollution Controls on Selected Food Industries - Vol. VII: The Grain Milling Industry (Draft), by Development Planning and Research Associates, June 1975 (Box 38, Folder 1196)
- Economic Impact of Water Pollution Controls on Selected Food Industries - Vol. VII: Final Version, November 1975 (Box 38, Folder 1197)
- Economic Impact of Water Pollution Controls on Selected Food Industries - Vol. VIII: The Leather Tanning Industry (Draft), by Development Planning and Research Associates, June 1975 (Box 39, Folder 1198)
- Economic Impact of Water Pollution Controls on Selected Food Industries - Vol. VIII: Final Version, November 1975 (Box 39, Folder 1199)
- Economic Impact of Water Pollution Controls on Selected Food Industries - Vol. IX: The Fertilizer Manufacturing Industry (Draft), by Development Planning and Research Associates, June 1975 (Box 39, Folder 1200)
- Economic Impact of Water Pollution Controls on Selected Food Industries - Vol. IX: Final Version, November 1975 (Box 39, Folder 1201)
- Economic Impact of Water Pollution Controls on Selected Food Industries - Addendum: Summary Tables (Draft), by Development Planning and Research Associates, August 1975 (Box 39, Folder 1202)
- Economic Impact of Water Pollution Controls on Selected Food Industries - Analysis of SEAS Results, International Research & Technology, December 1975 (Box 39, Folder 1203)
- Economic Impact of Water Pollution Controls on Selected Food Industries - Residual Forecasting Analysis, International Research & Technology, February 1976 (Box 39, Folder 1204)
- Economic Impact of Water Pollution Controls on Selected Food Industries - Macroeconomic Impacts of PL92-500 (Draft), by CONSAD, December 1975 (Box 39, Folder 1205)
- Economic Impact of Water Pollution Controls on Selected Food Industries - Macroeconomic Impacts of PL92-500, Final Version, by CONSAD, March 1976 (Box 39, Folder 1206)
- Economic Impact of Water Pollution Controls on Selected Food Industries - Macroeconomic Impacts of PL92-500, Summary (Draft), by CONSAD, October 1975 (Box 39, Folder 1207)
- Economic Impact of Water Pollution Controls on Selected Food Industries - Implementation and Use of Phase III Capabilities in the SEAS, by Control Data, May 1974 (Box 39, Folder 1208)
- Economic Impact of Water Pollution Controls on Selected Food Industries - Assistance in the Modification and Use of SEAS: Final Progress Report, by Control Data, July 1976 (Box 39, Folder 1209)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Data Specifications (Box 39, Folder 1210)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Residuals Coefficients - Resgen Module (Box 39, Folder 1211)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - OBERS Projections: Economic Activity in the United States, 1929-2020, U.S. Water Resources Council, September 1972 (Box 39, Folder 1212)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - OBERS Projections: Population and Personal Income, U.S. Water Resources Council, March 1974 (Box 39, Folder 1213)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Program Specifications: SEAS Extensions to Inter-Industry Forecasting Model, Report to EPA, by Control Data (1 of 2), February 1974 (Box 39, Folder 1214)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Program Specifications: SEAS Extensions to Inter-Industry Forecasting Model, Report to EPA, by Control Data (2 of 2), February 1974 (Box 39, Folder 1215)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Capital Markets and Water Quality Needs: 1975-1985, by The Conference Board, July 1975 (Box 40, Folder 1216)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Distribution of Water Pollution Control Costs, Draft, by Urban Systems Research and Engineering, December 1975 (Box 40, Folder 1217)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Distribution of Water Pollution Control Costs, Vol. I, by Urban Systems Research and Engineering, March 1976 (Box 40, Folder 1218)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Distribution of Water Pollution Control Costs, Vol. II, by Urban Systems Research and Engineering, March 1976 (Box 40, Folder 1219)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Developing a 50-State Model for Forecasting the Fiscal Situation for State-Local Governments, Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations, July 1974 (Box 40, Folder 1220)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Financing PL92-500: A Study of State and Local Government Budgets, Vol. I, by Data Resources, October 1975 (Box 40, Folder 1221)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Financing PL92-500: A Study of State and Local Government Budgets, Vol. II, by Data Resources, October 1975 (Box 40, Folder 1222)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Financing PL92-500: A Study of State and Local Government Budgets, Vol. III, by Data Resources, October 1975 (Box 40, Folder 1223)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Financing PL92-500: The Impact of the Federal Water Pollution Control Act of 1972 on the Municipal Bond Market (Draft), by Data Resources, September 1975 (Box 40, Folder 1224)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Financing PL92-500: Vol. II (Draft), by Data Resources, September 1975 (Box 40, Folder 1225)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Financing PL92-500: Appendix (Draft), by Data Resources, September 1975 (Box 40, Folder 1226)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Financing PL92-500: Vol. I (Summary of Reports), by Data Resources, August 1975 (Box 40, Folder 1227)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Municipal Choice of Options for Meeting Effluent Limitations and Goals (Draft), by Meta Systems, July 1975 (Box 40, Folder 1228)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Municipal Choice Among Waste Treatment Options, by Meta Systems, December 1975 (Box 40, Folder 1229)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Irrigation Return Flows and Pollutant Run-off from Nonirrigated Agriculture (Draft), by the Center for Agricultural and Rural Development, Iowa State University, July 1975 (Box 40, Folder 1230)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Irrigation Return Flows and Pollutant Run-off from Nonirrigated Agriculture, Final Report, Center for Agricultural and Rural Development, Iowa State University, July 1975 (Box 40, Folder 1231)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Analysis of the Agricultural Impacts Study by Iowa State University, by Management Science Systems, August 1975 (Box 40, Folder 1232)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Effects of Effluent Discharge Limitations on Foreign Trade (Draft), by Public Research Institute, June 1975 (Box 40, Folder 1233)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Effects of Effluent Discharge Limitations on Foreign Trade (Final Report), by Public Research Institute, February 1976 (Box 40, Folder 1234)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Impact on Residential Property Prices of Future Levels of Water Quality (Draft) by David M. Dornbusch and Co., May 1975 (Box 41, Folder 1235)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Impact of Water Quality Improvements on Residential Property Prices, by David M. Dornbusch and Co., December 1975 (Box 41, Folder 1236)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Water Related Recreation Benefits from PL92-500, Vol. I, by National Planning Association, November 1975 (Box 41, Folder 1237)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Water Related Recreation Benefits from PL92-500, Vol. II, by National Planning Association, November 1975 (Box 41, Folder 1238)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Water Related Recreation Benefits from PL92-500, Appendices, by National Planning Association, November 1975 (Box 41, Folder 1239)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Benefits to Commercial and Recreational Fisheries from Quality of Coastal Waters, Vol. I (Draft), by Florida State University, July 1975 (Box 41, Folder 1240)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Benefits to Commercial and Recreational Fisheries from Quality of Coastal Waters, Vol. II (Draft), by Florida State University, July 1975 (Box 41, Folder 1241)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Benefits from Water Pollution Abatement, Coastal Waters, Vol. I, by Florida State University, April 1976 (Box 41, Folder 1242)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Benefits from Water Pollution Abatement, Coastal Waters, Vol. II, by Florida State University, April 1976 (Box 41, Folder 1243)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Water Quality Improvements on Public Swimming (Draft), by Battelle Memorial Institute, July 1975 (Box 41, Folder 1244)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Benefits from Water Pollution Abatement: Beach Closings and Reopenings, by Battelle Memorial Institute, February 1976 (Box 41, Folder 1245)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Lake Washington-Lake Union: Social Impact Study (Draft), by Human Resources Planning Institute, June 1975 (Box 41, Folder 1246)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Social Impacts of PL92-500, by Human Resources Planning Institute, December 1975 (Box 41, Folder 1247)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Summary of the Social Impact Studies, by Human Resources Planning Institute, January 1976 (Box 41, Folder 1248)
- Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Effluent Charges: Papers by Susan Rose-Ackerman (September 1975), Otto Davis (June 1976), Gardner Brown (August 1975) and Allan Kneese (August 1975) (Box 42, Folder 1249)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Boston Harbor/Charles River (Draft), by Process Research, June 1975 (Box 42, Folder 1250)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Boston Harbor/Charles River, Environmental Research & Technology, April 1976 (Box 42, Folder 1251)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Connecticut River Basin, by the Center for the Environment and Man, April 1975 (Box 42, Folder 1252)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Housatonic River (Draft), by Lawler, Matusky and Skelly Engineers, June 1975 (Box 42, Folder 1253)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Housatonic River (Final Report), by Lawler, Matusky and Skelly Engineers (1 of 2), December 1975 (Box 42, Folder 1254)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Housatonic River (Final Report), by Lawler, Matusky and Skelly Engineers (2 of 2), December 1975 (Box 42, Folder 1255)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Potomac River (Draft), Academy of Natural Sciences of Philadelphia, July 1975 (Box 42, Folder 1256)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Potomac River (Final Report), by the Academy of Natural Sciences of Philadelphia, July 1975 (Box 42, Folder 1257)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Potomac Estuary (Draft), by GKY and Associates, January 1975 (Box 42, Folder 1258)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Potomac Estuary (Final Report), by GKY and Associates, January 1975 (Box 42, Folder 1259)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Saint John River, Maine (Draft), by Meta Systems, April 1975 (Box 42, Folder 1260)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Saint John River, Maine, by Meta Systems (1 of 2), December 1975 (Box 42, Folder 1261)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Saint John River, Maine, by Meta Systems (2 of 2), December 1975 (Box 42, Folder 1262)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Susquehanna River, Final Report, Lawler, Matusky, and Skelly Engineers (1 of 2), December 1975 (Box 42, Folder 1263)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Susquehanna River, Final Report, Lawler, Matusky, and Skelly Engineers (2 of 2), December 1975 (Box 43, Folder 1264)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Chesapeake Bay, Vol. I, Water Quality, by Virginia Institute of Marine Science, June 1975 (Box 43, Folder 1265)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Chesapeake Bay, Vol. II, Ecological Conditions, by Virginia Institute of Marine Science, June 1975 (Box 43, Folder 1266)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Escambia River and Bay, Florida, Executive Summary Draft, by Atlantis Scientific, May 1975 (Box 43, Folder 1267)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Escambia River and Bay, Florida, Draft, by Atlantis Scientific, May 1975 (Box 43, Folder 1268)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Escambia River and Bay, Florida, Final Report, by Atlantis Scientific, May 1976 (Box 43, Folder 1269)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Mississippi-Minnesota-St. Croix Confluences, Draft, Midwest Research Institute, May 1975 (Box 43, Folder 1270)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Mississippi-Minnesota-St. Croix Confluences, by Midwest Research Institute, March 1976 (Box 43, Folder 1271)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Upper Mississippi River Basin, Final Report, by Water Resources Engineers, July 1975 (Box 43, Folder 1272)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Santee River Basin, Draft, by Academy of Natural Sciences of Philadelphia, July 1975 (Box 43, Folder 1273)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Santee River Basin, Final Report, by Academy of Natural Sciences of Philadelphia, July 1975 (Box 43, Folder 1274)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Santee River Basin, Section II: Final Report, by Water Resources Engineers, April 1975 (Box 43, Folder 1275)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Trinity River Basin, Draft, by Water Resources Engineers, May 1975 (Box 43, Folder 1276)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Trinity River Basin, by Water Resources Engineers, May 1976 (Box 43, Folder 1277)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Yadkin-Pee Dee River Basin, by TRW Transportation and Environmental Operations, May 1975 (Box 43, Folder 1278)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Iowa-Cedar Rivers Basin, Draft, by Midwest Research Institute, May 1975 (Box 44, Folder 1279)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Iowa-Cedar Rivers Basin, by Midwest Research Institute, March 1976 (Box 44, Folder 1280)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Iowa-Cedar Rivers Basin, Section II: Final Report, by Water Resources Engineers, July 1975 (Box 44, Folder 1281)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Lower Missouri River, Draft, by Midwest Research Institute, June 1975 (Box 44, Folder 1282)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Lower Missouri River, Final Report, by Midwest Research Institute, December 1975 (Box 44, Folder 1283)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Guadalupe-San Antonio River Basin, Draft, Water Resources Engineers, May 1975 (Box 44, Folder 1284)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Guadalupe-San Antonio River Basin, by Water Resources Engineers, March 1976 (Box 44, Folder 1285)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - South Platte River, Draft, by Tetra Tech, May 1975 (Box 44, Folder 1286)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - South Platte River, by Tetra Tech, December 1975 (Box 44, Folder 1287)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Upper Rio Grande, Section II: Studies, Final Report, by Water Resources Engineers, March 1975 (Box 44, Folder 1288)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Upper Rio Grande, Draft, by the Academy of Natural Sciences of Philadelphia, June 1975 (Box 44, Folder 1289)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Upper Rio Grande, Final Report, by the Academy of Natural Sciences of Philadelphia, June 1975 (Box 44, Folder 1290)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Alaska, Gulf of, Draft, by Tetra Tech, May 1975 (Box 44, Folder 1291)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Alaska, Gulf of, Final Report, by Tetra Tech, February 1976 (Box 45, Folder 1292)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Lower Columbia River, Draft, by Tetra Tech, February 1975 (Box 45, Folder 1293)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Lower Columbia River, Final Report, by Tetra Tech, February 1976 (Box 45, Folder 1294)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Columbia River, Draft, by Parametrix, May 1975 (Box 45, Folder 1295)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Columbia River, Final Report, by Parametrix (1 of 2), December 1975 (Box 45, Folder 1296)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Columbia River, Final Report, by Parametrix (2 of 2), December 1975 (Box 45, Folder 1297)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Hawaii, Draft, by Tetra Tech, May 1975 (Box 45, Folder 1298)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Hawaii, Final Report, by Tetra Tech, February 1976 (Box 45, Folder 1299)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Puerto Rico, Draft, by Tetra Tech, May 1975 (Box 45, Folder 1300)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Puerto Rico, Final Report, by Tetra Tech, February 1976 (Box 45, Folder 1301)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Snake River, Idaho, Draft, by Tetra Tech, February 1975 (Box 45, Folder 1302)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Snake River, Idaho, Final Report, by Tetra Tech, February 1976 (Box 45, Folder 1303)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Snake River, Draft, by Parametrix, April 1975 (Box 45, Folder 1304)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Snake River, Final Report, by Parametrix, January 1976 (Box 45, Folder 1305)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Southern California Bight, Draft, by Tetra Tech, May 1975 (Box 45, Folder 1306)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Southern California Bight, Final Report, by Tetra Tech, February 1976 (Box 45, Folder 1307)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Biscayne Bay (Draft), Water Resources Engineers, May 1975 (Box 45, Folder 1308)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Biscayne Bay (Final Report), Water Resources Engineers, March 1976 (Box 45, Folder 1309)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Hudson River (Draft), Lawler, Matusky and Skilly Engineers, (1 of 4) Chapters I-III, August 1975 (Box 46, Folder 1310)